ASHISH MISHRA

UI DEVELOPER | UX SPECIALIST

+91 8506848797

ASHISHMISHRA221984@GMAIL.

https://github.com/ashishui

Summary

Focused and quick learning Software Engineer with 9+ years of experience in designing and developing complex e-learning solutions and web applications. Ability to plan, develop and implement successful large-scale projects from conception to completion. Specializes in Angular, Javascript, HTML5 and CSS3. Experience in full Agile projects.

Skills

Javascript | ES6 | Angular |
Typescript | NgRx | Angular
Material | Ngx Bootstrap |
Angularjs | Backbonejs | Bootstrap
| Responsive design | HTML5 |
CSS3 | LESS/SASS | Action script
2.0, 3.0 | GIT | SVN | AGILE

Experience

GENPACT HEADSTRONG CAPITAL MARKETS | LEAD CONSULTANT July 2012 – Present | NOIDA

- Development of new features and bug fixing
- Learned Agile model of software development and took ownership of all coding and testing
- Implemented multiple item drag and drop feature in Angular
- Creating UI solutions utilizing agile process
- Functional Testing of various test case scenarios

HCL TECHNOLOGIES | LEAD ENGINEER

Feb 2010 - June 2012 | NOIDA

Bug fixing for mobile app

FUTURE SOFT INDIA PVT LTD | WEB DEVELOPER

JAN 2008 - Feb 2010 | DELHI

- Only frontend senior dev in team
- Designing of reusable components
- Evaluating requirements and preparing functional mockups
- Guiding team to follow best practices
- Unit and Integration testing
- Carried out UAT deployment using Bamboo

Education

B.Tech(Computer Science): Institue of Integral Technology, Lucknow, 68.5% (2003-2007)

Intermediate(PCM): Aminabad Inter College, Lucknow, 58.4% (2001)

High School: Aminabad Inter College, Lucknow, 69% (1999)